Now, let me just clear up some things for you because the gaslighting is lighter ring.
One, there is a genocide happening in Palestine, no matter what anybody tells you.
Two, America is a racist country, no matter what anybody tells you.
Three, climate change is real.
The earth is absolutely on some other shit, no matter what nobody tells you.
And four, green bean casserole really is over.
It's done.
Don't nobody want it, no matter what nobody tells you.
Hope that set some things straight for you.
And if you don't believe me, there is a whole Google that you can look at to confirm it.
Now, let me go take these braids out because I am representing the diaspora in multiple ways.
We got an Afro and then we got a Senegalese twist at the same damn time.
Can't nobody say I'm not.
Black, black, new growth.
Black, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue